Mina Bassley

9101 Apple St, Bryn Mawr, PA 12345 mina_bassley@mail.com (267) 210-0293

PROFILE

Sales account executive with three years of professional experience, specializing in maintaining customer accounts, supporting sales cycles, and qualifying leads. Adept at closing new business and interfacing with prospects and potential clients. A strong background in identifying process improvements to enhance the sales process.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Sales Account Executive

Marketing CRM Incorporated, Philadelphia, PA | January 2020 - Present

- Collaborate with a team of sales account executives and management teams to review sales processes, identify gaps, and recommend improvements
- Analyze sales data, conduct reporting, and deliver reports to leadership
- Serve as the point of contact for customer issues, which include analyzing client business needs and identifying appropriate solutions
- Oversaw eight client accounts generating \$20K to \$50K in revenue, interfaced with customers, fielded client issues, and attended meetings with the Head of Sales

Sales Representative

Customer Journeys, Philadelphia, PA | January 2019-January 2020

- Conducted cold calling and prospecting
- Qualified inbound and outbound sales leads, supported the sales process, and achieved 120% of sales quota for 2019
- Attended meetings with prospects and collaborated with Sales Manager to close new business and recommend products in alignment with client needs
- Created sales reports using Microsoft Excel and delivered findings to the sales team during weekly, monthly, and quarterly meetings

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Marketing

Pennsylvania State University University Park, PA September 2015 - May 2019

KEY SKILLS

- Lead Qualification
- Relationship Building
- Prospecting
- Customer Success
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)